( knocking )
HEY.
MONICA?
WHAT TIME IS IT?
AH, 9:00.
BUT IT'S DARK OUT.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU ALWAYS SLEEP
TILL NOON, SILLY.
THIS IS WHAT
9:00 LOOKS LIKE.
I GUESS I'LL GET WASHED UP THEN.
WATCH THAT SUN RISE.
I'M REALLY GETTING TIRED OF
SNEAKING AROUND ALL THE TIME.
I KNOW. ME TOO.
HEY, WHAT IF WE WENT AWAY
FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND?
YOU KNOW, HAD NO INTERRUPTIONS.
AND WE COULD BE NAKED
THE ENTIRE TIME.
ALL WEEKEND?
THAT'S A WHOLE LOT OF NAKED.
YEAH, I COULD SAY
THAT I HAVE A CONFERENCE
AND YOU CAN SAY
YOU HAVE A CHEF THING.
OH, I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO GO TO THIS CULINARY FAIR
THAT THEY HAVE IN JERSEY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE NOT, THOUGH.
LET'S GO.
WAIT, WHAT ABOUT JOEY?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
GUESS WHAT I'M DOING
THIS WEEKEND?
THIS CULINARY FAIR
IN JERSEY.
HOW WEIRD.
CHANDLER JUST TOLD US
HE'S GOT A CONFERENCE THERE.
OH, WELL, THAT'S FUNNY.
SEEMS LIKE CHANDLER'S CONFERENCE
COULD HAVE BEEN
IN CONNECTICUT OR VERMONT.
I'M NOT IN CHARGE OF WHERE
THE CONFERENCE IS HELD.
DO YOU WANT PEOPLE TO THINK
IT'S A FAKE CONFERENCE?
IT'S A REAL CONFERENCE.
HEY. IS RACHEL HERE?
I'VE GOT TO TALK TO HER.
NO, SHE'S OUT SHOPPING.
DAMN.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I TOLD EMILY TO COME
AND I JUST NEED TO, YOU KNOW,
TALK TO RACHEL ABOUT IT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
SO, WHEN EMILY COMES
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SEE RACHEL ANYMORE?
WELL, LOOK.
I'M JUST TRYING TO FOCUS
ON THE "I GET TO SEE MY WIFE"
PART, ALL RIGHT.
AND NOT THE PART
THAT MAKES ME DO THIS.
SO YOU GUYS ARE
NEVER GOING
TO BE IN THE SAME
ROOM TOGETHER?
HOW IS THAT
GOING TO WORK?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I MEAN, BUT I ASSURE YOU,
I WILL FIGURE IT OUT.
DOESN'T SEEM LIKE
IT'S GOING TO WORK.
HI, GUYS.
HI.
HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'RE FLIPPING
MONICA'S MATTRESS.
SO I'M THINKING BASICALLY, WE
PICK IT UP AND THEN WE FLIP IT.
THAT'S BETTER
THAN MY WAY.
OH, OKAY. HEY, GUYS.
WOULD YOU FLIP MINE TOO?
( all groaning )
OH, LOOK.
A LETTER FROM MY MOM.
SO, RACH...
YOU KNOW HOW EMILY
IS COMING, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH. I KNOW.
CAN YOU HEAR ANYTHING?
OH, YES. SOMEBODY JUST SAID,
"CAN YOU HEAR ANYTHING?"
HEY, JOEY'S ASS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, REMEMBER WHEN THEY GOT
INTO THAT BIG FIGHT
AND BROKE UP AND WE WERE ALL
STUCK IN HERE ALL NIGHT
WITH NO FOOD OR ANYTHING?
WELL, WHEN ROSS SAID
RACHEL AT THE WEDDING
I FIGURE IT WAS GOING
TO HAPPEN AGAIN, YOU KNOW.
SO I HID THIS IN HERE.
OOH. CANDY BARS,
CROSSWORD PUZZLES.
OOH, MAD LIBS, MINE.
CONDOMS?
HEY, YOU DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
WE'RE GOING TO BE IN HERE.
WE MAY HAVE TO REPOPULATE
THE EARTH.
AND CONDOMS ARE THE WAY
TO DO THAT?
ANYWAY, IT ALL
BOILS DOWN TO THIS.
THE LAST TIME
I TALKED TO EMILY...
OH, MY GOD! OUR DOG DIED.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD.
LAPOOH, OUR DOG.
LAPOOH'S STILL ALIVE?
OH, IT SAYS HE WAS HIT
BY AN ICE CREAM TRUCK.
AND DRAGGED
FOR NINE... TEEN BLOCKS.
OH, MY GOD.
SWEETIE, WE HEARD YOU CRYING.
PLEASE DON'T CRY.
IT'S LAPOOH.
I KNOW, IT'S LAPOOH RIGHT NOW,
BUT IT WILL GET BETTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE'RE HERE.
OOH, CHOCOLATES ON THE PILLOWS.
OH, I LOVE THAT.
OH, YOU SHOULD LIVE WITH JOEY.
ROLLOS EVERYWHERE.
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OH, YES.
GET IN HERE. THERE'S
A HIGH-SPEED CAR CHASE ON.
WE'RE SWITCHING ROOMS.
OH, DEAR GOD.
THEY GAVE US GLASSES.
NO, THEY GAVE US GLASSES
WITH LIPSTICK ON THEM.
I MEAN... IF THEY
DIDN'T CHANGE THE GLASSES
WHO KNOWS WHAT ELSE
THEY DIDN'T CHANGE.
OH, COME ON, SWEETIE.
I JUST WANT THIS WEEKEND
TO BE PERFECT, OKAY.
WE CAN CHANGE ROOMS, CAN'T WE?
OKAY, BUT LET'S DO IT NOW
BECAUSE CHOPPER 5
JUST LOST ITS FEED.
HEY, SO, AH, YOU KNOW
HOW THERE WAS SOMETHING
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT?
OH, YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW I'M TRYING
TO WORK THINGS OUT WITH EMILY?
WELL, THERE'S THIS ONE THING.
OKAY...
HERE GOES.
I MADE A PROMISE THAT...
OH, HEY.
WHAT?
YOUR NOSE IS BLEEDING.
OH, GOD.
OH, NOT AGAIN.
THIS HAPPENED
WHEN MY GRANDFATHER DIED.
IT'S...
I'M SORRY.
OH, GROSS.
OKAY, SO I'M SORRY.
WHAT DID YOU WANT TO TELL ME?
UH...
( snorts )
SORRY.
I, UH...
I CAN'T SEE YOU ANYMORE.
I KNOW, IT'S RIDICULOUS.
I CAN'T SEE YOU EITHER.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND THIS ROOM
MORE TO YOUR LIKING.
OKAY, GREAT.
THEY SAY HE'S ONLY GOT
HALF A TANK LEFT.
HALF A TANK. WE STILL GOT A LOT
OF HIGH-SPEED CHASING TO DO.
WE'RE SWITCHING ROOMS AGAIN.
WHAT? WHY?
THIS IS A GARDEN VIEW ROOM AND
WE PAID FOR AN OCEAN VIEW ROOM.
OUR LAST OCEAN VIEW ROOM
WAS UNACCEPTABLE TO YOU.
EXCUSE ME.
UM, CAN I TALK TO YOU
OVER HERE FOR JUST A SECOND?
UH-HUH.
CHANDLER?
YEAH.
OKAY, LOOK.
THESE CLOWNS ARE TRYING
TO TAKE US FOR A RIDE
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LET THEM.
NOW, WE'RE NOT
A COUPLE OF SUCKERS.
I HEAR YA, MUGSY.
BUT LOOK, ALL THESE ROOMS
ARE FINE, OKAY.
CAN YOU JUST PICK ONE
SO I CAN WATCH THE...
HAVE A PERFECT MAGICAL WEEKEND
TOGETHER WITH YOU?
OKAY, THIS ONE I LIKE.
NOTHING.
NOTHING, IT'S OVER.
DAMN IT. THIS IS REGULARLY
SCHEDULED PROGRAMMING.
CAN WE TURN THE TV OFF?
DO WE REALLY WANT TO SPEND
THE ENTIRE WEEKEND LIKE THIS?
OH, I'M SORRY. AM I
GETTING IN THE WAY
OF ALL THE
ROOM-SWITCHING FUN?
DON'T BLAME ME
FOR RUINING TONIGHT.
WHO SHOULD I BLAME?
THE NICE BELLMAN
WHO DRAGGED OUR LUGGAGE
TO TEN DIFFERENT ROOMS?
HOW ABOUT THE IDIOT
WHO THOUGHT HE COULD DRIVE
FROM ALBANY TO CANADA
ON HALF A TANK OF GAS?
DO NOT SPEAK ILL
OF THE DEAD.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE SPENDING
A ROMANTIC WEEKEND TOGETHER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
I JUST WANT TO WATCH
A LITTLE TELEVISION.
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
GEEZ, RELAX, MOM.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I SAID, GEEZ,
RELAX, MONNN.
HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
RACHEL, I'VE BEEN WANTING
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING
FOR A WHILE NOW
AND I REALLY...
I JUST HAVE TO GET IT OUT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT. WHAT'S UP?
OKAY...
YOU KNOW HOW YOU TOLD ME
I SHOULD DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO FIX MY MARRIAGE?
YEAH. I TOLD YOU TO GIVE EMILY
WHATEVER SHE WANTS.
AND WHILE THAT WAS GOOD ADVICE
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT
WHAT SHE WANTS...
YEAH?
IS FOR ME NOT
TO SEE YOU ANYMORE.
WELL, THAT'S CRAZY.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO TELL HER?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'VE ALREADY AGREED TO THIS,
HAVEN'T YOU?
IT'S AWFUL, I KNOW.
I... I MEAN, I FEEL TERRIBLE
BUT I HAVE TO DO THIS
IF I WANT MY MARRIAGE TO WORK.
AND I DO.
I HAVE TO MAKE
THIS MARRIAGE WORK.
I HAVE TO.
BUT THE GOOD THING IS
WE CAN STILL SEE EACH OTHER
UNTIL SHE GETS HERE.
OH!
OH, LUCKY ME!
OH, MY GOD,
THAT IS GOOD NEWS, ROSS.
I THINK
THAT'S THE BEST NEWS
I'VE HEARD SINCE LAPOOH DIED.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT A NIGHTMARE THIS HAS BEEN.
THIS IS SO HARD.
OH, YEAH, REALLY.
IS IT, ROSS?
YEAH, OKAY.
WELL, LET ME JUST MAKE THIS
A LITTLE EASIER FOR YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
STORMING OUT.
RACHEL, THIS IS YOUR APARTMENT.
YEAH, WELL,
THAT'S HOW MAD I AM.
DAMN ROLLOS!
HEY, YOU'RE BACK.
HEY.
HOW WAS YOUR CONFERENCE?
IT WAS TERRIBLE.
I FOUGHT WITH MY COLLEAGUES
THE ENTIRE TIME.
ARE YOU KIDDING WITH THIS?
( candy clatters )
SO YOUR WEEKEND
WAS A TOTAL BUST?
UH, NO. I SAW DONALD TRUMP
WAITING FOR AN ELEVATOR.
OH.
HI.
HEY, YOU'RE BACK, TOO.
YEAH. CHANDLER,
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR JUST A SECOND?
HOW WAS YOUR CHEF THING?
IT WAS AWFUL.
GUESS SOME PEOPLE JUST DON'T
APPRECIATE REALLY GOOD FOOD.
WELL, MAYBE IT WAS
THE KIND OF FOOD
THAT TASTED GOOD AT FIRST
BUT THEN MADE EVERYBODY VOMIT
AND HAVE DIARRHEA.
CHANDLER?
MONICA?
OKAY. I'D LIKE TO KNOW
HOW MUCH THE ROOM WAS
'CAUSE I WANT
TO PAY MY HALF.
OKAY, FINE. $300.
$300?
YEAH. JUST THINK OF IT
AS $25 PER ROOM.
( groans )
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
WOOFING ABOUT?
CHANDLER STOLE A 20
FROM MY PURSE.
NO!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT
I CONSTANTLY FIND
MYSELF WITHOUT 20s
AND YOU ALWAYS HAVE LOTS.
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
THE LOOK ON HER FACE.
I DON'T WANT RACHEL
TO HATE ME.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
DO YOU WANT MY ADVICE?
YES, PLEASE.
YOU WON'T LIKE IT.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU GOT MARRIED TOO FAST.
THAT'S NOT ADVICE.
I TOLD YOU.
I'M GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
MAN, IF ANYONE ASKED ME
TO GIVE UP ANY OF YOU
I DON'T THINK
I COULD DO IT.
ME, NEITHER.
MAYBE I COULD DO IT.
HI.
HI, RACH.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU GUYS
HEARD ABOUT THE WHOLE THING
WITH ME AND ROSS
BUT, YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
OBSESSING ABOUT IT ALL DAY
AND I WOULD JUST LOVE
NOT TO TALK ABOUT IT, ALL
RIGHT?
UH, I DON'T KNOW IF THIS
FALLS UNDER THAT CATEGORY
BUT, UH, ROSS IS
RIGHT BACK THERE.
THAT'S NOT ROSS.
OH, NO. NOT THAT GUY.
HE DOES LOOK LIKE HIM, THOUGH.
OKAY. ROSS IS IN THE BATHROOM.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S HAPPENING.
IT'S ALREADY STARTED.
I'M KIP.
YOU'RE NOT KIP.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHO KIP IS?
WHO CARES?
YOU'RE RACHEL.
WHO'S KIP?
KIP, MY OLD ROOMMATE.
WE ALL USED TO
HANG OUT TOGETHER?
OH, THAT POOR BASTARD.
SEE? YOU TOLD ME THE STORY.
HE AND MONICA DATED.
WHEN THEY BROKE UP
THEY COULDN'T EVEN BE
IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER
AND YOU ALL PROMISED
YOU WOULD STAY HIS FRIEND
AND WHAT HAPPENED?
HE GOT PHASED OUT.
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE PHASED OUT.
WELL, OF COURSE, I AM.
IT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN TO ROSS.
HE'S YOUR BROTHER.
HE'S YOUR OLD
COLLEGE ROOMMATE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMEONE HAD
TO LEAVE THE GROUP.
I ALWAYS ASSUMED
IT WOULD BE PHOEBE.
UH!
COME ON. YOU LIVE FAR AWAY,
YOU'RE NOT RELATED
YOU LIFT RIGHT OUT.
HEY.
HEY, MR. BING.
THAT HOTEL
YOU STAYED AT CALLED.
SAID SOMEONE LEFT
AN EYELASH CURLER IN YOUR ROOM.
YES, THAT WAS MINE.
'CAUSE I FIGURED
YOU HOOKED UP WITH SOME GIRL
AND SHE LEFT IT.
YES, THAT WOULD HAVE
MADE MORE SENSE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T EVEN FEEL
LIKE I KNOW YOU ANYMORE, MAN.
ALL RIGHT? LOOK
I'M JUST GOING TO ASK YOU THIS
ONE TIME, ALL RIGHT?
WHATEVER YOU SAY,
I'LL BELIEVE YOU.
WERE YOU OR WERE YOU NOT
ON A GAY CRUISE?
PHOEBE?
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE WHOLE
LIFTING-OUT THING.
LOOK, YOU GOT
TO COME WITH ME.
COME WHERE?
WHEREVER I GO.
COME ON.
YOU AND ME--
WE'LL START A NEW GROUP.
WE'RE THE BEST ONES.
OKAY, BUT TRY
TO GET JOEY, TOO.
PHEEBS, DO YOU MIND
IF I SPEAK TO RACHEL
ALONE FOR A SEC?
OH, SURE. YEAH.
BYE, ROSS...
( whispers ):
FOREVER.
HI.
HI. WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ISN'T THIS AGAINST THE RULES?
I TALKED TO MONICA.
LOOK, I'M THE ONE
WHO MADE THE CHOICE.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S
MAKING THINGS CHANGE
SO I SHOULD BE THE ONE
TO, YOU KNOW, STEP BACK.
OH, ROSS...
NO. NO, IT'S
OKAY, REALLY.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF PEOPLE
WHO JUST SEE THEIR SISTERS
AT THANKSGIVING
AND JUST SEE THEIR COLLEGE
ROOMMATES AT REUNIONS
AND JUST SEE JOEY
AT BURGER KING.
SO, IS THAT BETTER?
NO, IT'S NOT BETTER.
I STILL DON'T GET
TO SEE YOU.
WELL, WHAT WOULD
YOU DO, RACH?
IF YOU WERE ME,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
WELL, FOR STARTERS
I WOULD HAVE SAID
THE RIGHT NAME
AT MY WEDDING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
I KNOW.
I AM SO SORRY.
I KNOW THAT, TOO.
( clears throat )
HEY, RACH?
SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
BUT PHOEBE SAID
YOU WANT TO TALK TO ME
ABOUT A TRIP OR SOMETHING.
HEY.
HI.
I JUST CAME OVER
TO DROP OFF... NOTHING.
SO, THAT WEEKEND
KIND OF SUCKED, HUH?
YEAH, IT DID.
SO I GUESS THIS IS OVER.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU AND ME.
IT HAD TO END SOMETIME.
WHY, EXACTLY?
BECAUSE OF THE WEEKEND.
WE HAD A FIGHT.
CHANDLER, THAT'S CRAZY.
IF YOU GIVE UP
EVERY TIME
YOU HAVE A FIGHT
WITH SOMEONE
YOU'D NEVER BE WITH
ANYONE LONGER THAN...
OH!
SO, THIS ISN'T OVER?
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
NO, NO.
IT WAS A FIGHT.
YOU DEAL WITH IT
AND YOU MOVE ON.
IT'S NOTHING
TO FREAK OUT ABOUT.
REALLY? OKAY. GREAT.
AW...
WELCOME TO AN ADULT
RELATIONSHIP.
WE'RE IN A RELATIONSHIP?
I'M AFRAID SO.
OKAY.
HEY.
OH, HEY, MONICA.
I HEARD YOU SAW
DONALD TRUMP
AT YOUR CONVENTION.
YEAH. SAW HIM WAITING
FOR AN ELEVATOR.
Monica:
HEY, RACH,
CAN I BORROW
YOUR EYELASH CURLER?
I LOST MINE.
IT'S IN THE BATHROOM.
OH!
JOEY, CAN I TALK
TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
OOH! OH!
I NEED TO TALK
TO YOU RIGHT NOW.
OH! OH! OH!
OH...!
YES.
YOU AND, AND YOU?
YES, BUT YOU CANNOT
TELL ANYONE.
NO ONE KNOWS.
HOW? WHEN?
IT HAPPENED IN LONDON.
IN LONDON!
THE REASON
WE DIDN'T TELL ANYONE
WAS 'CAUSE WE DIDN'T WANT
TO MAKE A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT.
BUT IT IS A BIG DEAL.
I HAVE TO TELL SOMEONE!
YOU CAN'T.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
WE JUST DON'T WANT
TO DEAL WITH TELLING
EVERYONE, OKAY?
JUST PROMISE
YOU WON'T TELL.
ALL RIGHT!
MAN, THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, IT'S GREAT!
BUT...
I KNOW, IT'S GREAT.
I DON'T WANT
TO SEE THAT.
WE'RE SO STUPID.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THERE?
THEY'RE TRYING TO TAKE JOEY.
"THE POPULAR PHOEBE IN TENNIS
IS THE 'OVERHAND PHOEBE'
"AND IF YOU WIN, YOU MUST SLAP
YOUR OPPONENT ON THE PHOEBE
AND SAY, 'MY PHOEBE.'"
THAT'S CUTE.
WE REALLY ALL ENJOYED IT,
BUT YOU KNOW IT DOESN'T COUNT.
COUNT FOR WHAT?
JUST COUNT IN OUR HEADS
AS GOOD MAD LIBS.
I'M DONE.
IT'S OVER.
NO, WAIT. WAIT, GUYS,
IF WE FOLLOW THE RULES
IT'S STILL FUN
AND IT MEANS SOMETHING.
I'M GOING
TO TAKE OFF.
GUYS, RULES ARE GOOD.
RULES HELP CONTROL THE FUN.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]